>> Jem Young: 我们在使用旧协议之前讨论的所有内容
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Everything we were
discussing before use the old protocol
HTTP1.1。
HTTP1.1.
这是 89年发明的吗
This was invented in 89?
1.0 ?
1.0?
1.1 就像 98 之类的
And 1.1 was like 98 or
something like that.
我猜到日期了但我想我是对的
I'm guessing on the dates but
I think I'm about right.
但这一协议只是每个人都同意的标准。
But again this protocol is just
a standard that everybody agreed on.
是最新最伟大的东西直到人们说你知道什么
HTTP1.1 was the latest and
greatest until people said you know what?
这不为我们工作我们需要点不同的东西
This isn't working for us,
we need something a little bit different.
我们需要一些不只是 1.2 的东西，我们需要完全不同的东西。
We need something that not just 1.2, we
need something that's entirely different.
因此  来了，任何人，请原谅，任何人都知道  是什么吗 ?
Thus HTTP/2 came along, anybody,
excuse me, anybody know what HTTP/2 is?
>> Jem Young: 任何人，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Anybody, anybody, yes?
>> 扬声器 2: 这是流式包的一种方式
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It's a way
of streaming packets so
你有一个持续的联系
that you have a persistent connection and
您不必创建与每个请求链接的多个连接。
you don't have to create multiple
connections with each request link.
> > Jem Young: 是的，你接近了，你几乎是在描述，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah, you're close,
you're describing almost,
你开车去 HTTP/3
you're driving HTTP/3 actually.
很棒的工作但是我们跳得挺快的你就在右边的轨道上
So nice job, but we're jumping a little
ahead, you're on the right track, though.
有同样的答案吗
Get the same answer?
>> 扬声器 2: 是。 所以它依赖的是 SSL ，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah.
So it relies on SSL being in place,
您必须具有  设置。
you have to have HTTPS setup.
否则，它是 HTTP/2 的交易断路器。
Otherwise, it's a deal breaker for HTTP/2.
一旦你有了这个位置
Once you have that in place,
那是谷歌的 SPD 线，快速协议的扩展吗 ?
then it's an extension of
Google's SPD wire, speedy protocol?
但基本上它允许多路复用。
But basically it allows multiplexing.
>> Jem Young: 是- >> 演讲者 2: 这很重要。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yes-
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: That's a big deal.
> > Jem Young: [LAUGH] Nayled it ，再钉一次。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: [LAUGH] Nailed it,
nailed it again.
这就是为什么我们，再次，这个旅程，我们关注的是标题和
That's why we, again, this journey, we're
following from looking at the headers and
检查状态码，了解请求和响应的外观。
checking off status codes, we understand
what a request and response looks like.
要将  添加到我们的站点，现在我们将添加 。
To adding HTTPS to our site,
now we're gonna add HTTP/2.
由于 HTTP/2 的其中一个要求是首先启用了 SSL 。
Because one of the requirements for
HTTP/2 is you have SSL enabled first.
同样地，它们只是让你朝着正确的方向发展。
Again, they're just kinda nudging
you in the right direction.
你想用最先进的技术
You wanna use the latest
greatest technology.
你得加密了
You gotta have the encryption placed.
有了  就像阿达说的
With HTTP1.1, like Adar was just saying,
每个请求都有自己的线程它自己的管道
every single request had its own thread,
its own pipe.
因此，如果我想请求 main.js，请请求响应。
So if I wanna request main.js,
request response.
但记住这都是基于 TCP的
But remember, this is all over TCP,
并且 TCP 在发送这些 SYN 包时具有长的握手。
and TCP has that long handshake
where it sends those SYN packets.
然后发送确认包， ACK。
And then it send the acknowledge packets,
the ACK.
然后你把 SYN/ACK 发送回来，它叫做握手，
And then you send back SYN/ACK,
and it's called the handshake, and
真的很烦人
that's really cumbersome.
这意味着我想要的每一个资源
So that means every single
resource that I want,
需要单独的握手，让它在缺省情况下更慢。
is gonna need a separate handshake
which makes it slower by default.
使用  可以复用，因此
With HTTP/2 we can multiplex, so
你是对的我们可以把我们的联系流过去
you're right that we can
stream our connections over.
我们不是流的但我们可以建立一个联系
Well, we're not streaming but
we can make one connection.
然后我们就可以请求更大的管道了
Then we can request everything
just over a larger pipe.
而塞米提到了这一点，但这就是所谓的多路复用。
And Sammy mentioned it, but
that's what's known as multiplexing.
使用一个连接并通过单个连接执行多个操作。
Using one connection and doing multiple
things over a single connection.
所以我希望每次我都想要一个涂鸦
So instead of that, every single
time I want a dog.png, index.html,
我们会握手的
we do that handshake.
这会导致开销并增加使用的数据量。
Which causes overhead and
increase just an amount of data using.
我们只能通过一个连接
We can just do with one connection,
that said,
我们可以建立的联系数量有限。
there is a limit to the number
of connections we can make.
这在很大程度上取决于你的电脑。
And that's largely
depending on your computer.
我应该加上一个字条
I should add a side note,
这只是书呆子的问题我想是 10 个
this is just nerd trivia, and
I think it's ten, actually.
大家都做了，我觉得看浏览器和电脑，
People have done, I think it depends
on the browser and the computer,
就像这样
things like that.
>> 扬声器 2: 大多数浏览器限制为 6 个连接。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Most browsers
are limited to six connections.
>> Jem Young: 6?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Six?
我以为是十
I thought it was ten.
>> 扬声器 3: 它已更改。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: It changed.
>> Jem Young: 每个域。 >> 扬声器 3: 它已使用 6个。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Per domain.
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: It used to be six.
> > Jem Young: 不是十家吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: It's not ten?
>> 扬声器 3: 它取决于您的浏览器。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: It depends on your browser.
> > Jem Young: 是的，但这不像一颗银弹。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah, but
this isn't like a silver bullet.
没有，我可以建立一个联系，一切都通过它。
This isn't, I can make one connection and
everything goes through it.
您可以对每个连接进行最大数量的连接。
There is a maximum amount of connections
you can make per connection.
所以在很大程度上它会增加网络，你只会看到这些请求的失败，
So largely it'll be add networks,
you'll just see the deluge of requests,
就会有多个联系
that's gonna be multiple connections.
所以 HTTP/2 不是这神奇的东西但是
So HTTP/2 is not this magic thing but
however,
当你谈论发生的事情时就能摆脱这种握手
just getting rid of that handshake, when
you talk about something that happens.
什么规模大于 1 万亿?
What's bigger than a trillion?
我都不知道
I don't even know.
>> 演讲者 2: Quadrillion。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Quadrillion.
>> Jem Young: Quadrilion ，我们说的是四万亿的要求，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Quadrillion, we're
talking about quadrillions of requests,
每次都要摆脱这种握手，节省了大量的时间和精力，
getting rid of this handshake every single
time, saves a lot of time and energy and
就能更快地上网
just makes the internet faster.
所以，让我们添加 。
So let's add HTTP/2.
>> Jem Young: 这个比 Certbot 更容易。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: This one's
even easier than Certbot.
在  中，仅在 443 和 SSL 部分之间添加  。
In our nginx conf, just add HTTP/2
in between the 443 and the SSL part.
>> Jem Young: 对不起，我之前骗了你， Certbot 很容易。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: I'm sorry, I lied to
you before, Certbot was pretty easy.
这一个更容易
This one's even easier.
> > Jem Young: 我要继续做这个。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: I'm gonna go ahead and
do that.
我要上去下潜
I'm just gonna go up and come down
在此， >> Jem Young: 并开启 。
here,
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And turn on http2.
>> Jem Young: 接下来我也要在这里做
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And
then I'm gonna turn on http2 here as well.
> > Jem Young: 好的，有人输了，谁知道我在哪里 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Okay, anybody lost,
anybody know where I am?
如果您需要，如果在 nginx 配置的 blob 中找不到，
If you need to, if you can't find in
that blob of nginx configuration,
/443 并将您转至正确的位置。
/443 and
that'll take you to the right location.
>> Jem Young: Slash 只是 find 命令。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Slash is
just the find command.
> > Jem Young: 当我们完成后，我们就会像往常一样写和退出。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Then when we're done,
we want to write and quit as usual.
Wq 确保我们重新装入我们的 nginx。
Wq and make sure we reload our nginx.
因此 sudo 服务 nginx 重新装入。
So, sudo service nginx reload.
>> Jem Young: 我们来测试一下我们的网站。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And let's test out our site.
>> Jem Young: 嘿，漂亮的工作， Jem!
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Hey, nice work, Jem!
你可能不知道有什么区别
You probably don't notice a difference.
但如果你在你的任何一个浏览器里进了你的检查
But if you go into your inspector
in whatever browser you're using,
你可以看到 h2
you can see the h2.
这意味着您现在正在使用  协议。
That just means you are now
using HTTP/2 protocol.
>> Jem Young: 我认为有一个很好的演示。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And
I think there's a good demo.
让我看看能不能把这个拉上来
Let me see if I can pull this up here,
let's see.
Akamai
Akamai http2 demo, yeah,
我喜欢这个
I like this one.
>> Jem Young: 是的，我喜欢这个演示，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah, so I like this demo,
我没有包括它，因为我没有版权，但我可以给你看。
I didn't include it because I don't have
copyright on it, but I can show it to you.
这只是 Akamai 演示
This is just the Akamai demo,
说明  和 HTTP/2 之间的差异。
demonstrating the difference
between HTTP/1 and HTTP/2.
你看它真的有很大的图像，所以因为那个 multlexing，
You see it really with large images,
so because of that multplexing,
我可以请求一个图像。
I can request an image.
它只会把一块的管子从一个管子上
And it just sends down
the chunk over one pipe.
因为这不是握手，而是要快得多。
And because it's not doing that handshake,
it's much faster.
您认为它主要对您发送的大文件有好处。
You see it primarily the benefit on
large files you're sending down.
不是那么小，而是转向  那么痛苦和轻松。
Not so much small ones, but
turning HTTP/2, it's so painless and easy.
做得不痛，我们看到它很起码，我再跑一次。
It doesn't hurt to do it, we saw it's
pretty minimal, I'll run that again.
>> Jem Young: 不错，不错。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Not bad, not bad at all.
这就像我们能得到的那么简单
That was pretty as
straightforward as we can get.
这很容易
That was pretty easy.
我不是经常这样说，但那很容易，对吧 ?
I don't say that very often, but
that was pretty easy, right?
第二个优势是 HTTP/2 ，而多路复用是称为 HPACK的。
The second benefit to HTTP/2 besides that
multiplexing is something called HPACK.
HPACK 是一个压缩算法，但它不是
HPACK is a compression algorithm again,
but instead of,
让我跳回 >> Jem Young: 我会
let me jump back to the
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: I'll
跳转回标题部分。
jump back to the header section.
所以 HTTP/2 允许的是，大部分都是一样的。
So what HTTP/2 allows is,
most of these are the same.
我的用户代理程序通常不会在请求与
My user agent generally is not gonna
change magically between requests and
响应。
responses.
随着时间的推移我的接受不会改变
It's not gonna change over time,
my Accepts is not gonna change,
我的语言是不会改变的
my language isn't going to change.
那么 HPACK 压缩算法就是把所有这些头
So what the HPACK compression algorithm
does is it takes all these headers,
把它们压缩成一个杂凑
compresses them into a hash.
而它只是比较了它们的时间。
And it just compares them over time.
相比之下，我们大约有 30% ， 40% 的速度。
That comparison gives us about a 30,
40% speed up.
因为不是每次发送这些标题
Because instead of sending these
headers every single time,
它可以将这些向下压缩，然后按其意愿进行读取。
it can just compress these down and
then read them at will.
那是很有力量的，在多路复用中可能是次要的，
That's really powerful and that's beside
multiplexing is probably the secondary,
使用  的最强大的优势。
most powerful benefit of using HTTP/2.
这是我们得到的另一个速度，正在压缩这些标题。
That's the other speed up that we get,
is compressing those headers.
但记住， cookies 一般不能压缩。
But remember,
cookies can't be compressed generally.
你可以但它可能不会
You can, but it probably won't.
因为饼干随着时间的推移而变化，它们更有活力。
Because cookies change over time,
they're more dynamic.
因此，如果发送大量 cookie 有效内容，那么  无法帮助您。
So if you send a large cookie payload,
HTTP/2 is not gonna help you very much.
你想尽量减少你寄的饼干量
You wanna minimize the amount
of cookies you send.